Guide to the Bert N. Corona Papers, 1923-1984
Department of Special Collections
- Subject files, 1923-1983, Series 10
  - Immigration, 1967-1983, Sub-series 10.C
    - Voting rights for non-citizens, California Senate Bill 1307, by Senator Mervyn M. Dymally, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - La Voz del Barrio, flyers, (1) button, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Wall Street Journal on undocumented workers, May 2, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Welfare Policies on Aliens, HEW, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Western Center for Immigration Studies, budget, ca. 1977? (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - International Issues, 1971-1981, Sub-series 10.D
    - Acontecer Migratorio, Centro de Estudios de Pastoral Y Asistencia Migratoria (CEPAM), Venezuela, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - American Friends Service Committee, Mexico-U.S. economic relations, papers and clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Amnesty in Australia, by Desmond Storer, M.T. February 1977 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Arceo, Mendez, clippings, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Australian Immigrants, includes: Ethnic Rights Power and Participation, 1973;and But I wouldn't Want My Wife to Work Here..., A Study of Migrant Women in Melbourne Industry, ca. 1975 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Los Cambios en La Estructura del Proletariado Mexicano entre 1930 y 1960, Capítulo del libro Las Clase Obrera del México Actual, publicado en ruso, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Campa, Valentín; Communist Party candidate for the Presidency of Mexico, papers and clippings, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Centro Nacional de Comunicación Social, a.c., Mexico, articles, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - C.G.T. (Confederation General du Travail) 3rd Conference Nationale sur les Problems de L'Immigration, Montreuil, November 24-25, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - C.G.T. (Confederation General du Travail), publications and announcements, 1971-1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Chile, documents and posters, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Chile, documents and posters, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Chile, posters and bulletins, ca. 1974 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Chile Solidarity Committee, New York, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Christian Concern for Chile, newsletter, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Compañero, Revista Internacional del Ejército Guerrillero de los Pobres de Guatemala, ca., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Discrimination Against Migrant Workers in Europe, by Charles Barontini, submitted to the International Conference on Discrimination Against Migrant Workers in Europe, Geneva, September 1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Estados Unidos de América, Oficina Internacional del Trabajo, Serie Legislativa, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Guatemala, Two Priests Victimized, clipping, National Catholic Reporter, May 23, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Indochina Solidarity Committee Newsletter, vol. 2, no.2 June 24, 1974and vol. 2, no.3, August 10, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Information Services on Latin America (ISLA), Clipping Service, 456 clippings from major U.S. newspapers, October 6-18, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Information Services on Latin America (ISLA), bound index for July-December 1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Inter-American Foundation, Board of Directors, 1973 and 1977;Annual Report 1978; Summary of Grants, 1976-1978;clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Intergovernmental Committee for European Migration, press release, November 10, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions World Conference on Migrant and Stateless Workers, (4) page statement, Geneva 3-4, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - International Labor Conferences, correspondence, 1974, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - International NGO Conference (Non-governmental organizations) on Discrimination Against Migrant Workers in Europe, September 16-19, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Latin America, articles, 1970, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Latin American flyers and bulletins, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Latin American issues, includes: Chile, Cuba, and Mexico, flyers and poster, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Latin American labor solidarity movement, flyers, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Liaisons Internationales, Boletín Colegio San Justo, Sainst Just, Trujillo Alto, Abril-Junio, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Local 277 of the National Miners Union of Mexico call for support, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Mexican Labor Movement, history, ca. 1975 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Mexico, clippings, 1973, 1975; Mexico is Moving, But where?, by Carl T. Rowan and David M. Mazie, xerox, Reader's Digest, December 1976 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Mexico, economics, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Mexico-U.S. economic relations, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Mexico-U.S oil, No existen en la tierra dos naciones tan estrechamente entrelazadas, por Rodolfo Guzman, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Middle East, pamphlets and flyers, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Migrant Workers and Their Problems, [Europe] papers, clippings and flyers, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - The Multi-National Corporation, pamphlet by AFL-CIO, 1979? (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Peace, Sovereignty and Economic Independence: Documents of the Continental Conference of Latin American and the Caribbean, Mexico City, February 1-4, 1978,World Peace Council, (122) pages (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Resolution re: political prisoners in Mexican jails since 1968, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - El Salvador, Articles, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - El Salvador, Clippings, 1979, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - El Salvador, Clippings, 1980, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - El Salvador, flyers, news releases and bulletins, 1980, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - El Salvador, news releases and position papers, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - El Salvador, update, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Sindicatos de Mexico, lists of names and organizations, ca. 197?] (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - United States-Mexico Conference, Ciudad Juara, February/March 1980 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - La Universidad Internacional de México, S.C.L., course listing and schedule, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Journals, 1923-1982, Sub-series 10.A
    - Acapulco, Tourismo-Política, Sociales Y Deportes, [broken set], 1971-1976 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - AHORA [The Voice of the Farmworker and Mexican-Americans in Colorado], Alamosa, Colorado, 1973, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Aliso-Pico News, Los Angeles, October 1972 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - American Educator, American Federation of Teachers, Fall, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Boletin del Cpustal: Congreso Permanente de Unidad Sindical de los Trabajadores de América Latina, December 1978 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Boletín Informativo, Sobre Asuntos Migratorios Y Fronterizos, Del Comité de Serivicio de Los Amigos, Mayo-Junio 1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Bread and Justice, Interfaith Hunger Coalition of Southern California, Newsletter, 1980, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - The Catholic Agitator, [broken set], 1981 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Commerce: The Journal of Minority Business, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Corazón de Aztlan, January/February 1982 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Counter Spy, April/May 1979 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - CRIE (Centro Regional de Información Ecuménica), [broken set], 1979, 1977-1980 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - CRIE (Centro Regional de Información Ecuménica), [broken set], 1981 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Desde Uruguay, [broken set], 1978, 1980, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Di: Revista Política Semanal, Mexico, [broken set], 1980 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Di: Revista Política Semanal, Mexico, [broken set], 1980 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Dialogo Sindical: Boletín Mensual Informativo publicado por la Federación Sindical Mundial, 9 Deciembre de 1979;and Dialogo Sindical: Boletín para América Latina publicado por la Federación Sindical Mundial, Julio-Agosto, Septiembre-Octubre de 1980 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Don't Mourn, Organize! published by the United Struggle Press, New York, [broken set], April-December 1977 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Economic Notes, N.Y., Labor Research Association, October 1975 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Espartaco, xerox, Febrero de 1923 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Flashes: Del Mundo Sindical, [broken set], October 1975-December 8, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Flashes: Del Mundo Sindical, [broken set], 1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - El Foro del Pueblo: Al Serivicio del La Clase Trabajadora, Los Angeles, California, March 1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - HOY, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - International Affairs, Moscow, September 1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Labor Today, February 19, 1977, November, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - The Laborer, October 1980, February 1981 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Latin America and Empire Report, published by North American Congress on Latin America (NACLA), [broken set], 1975, 1976, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Leaves, from the Mariannhill Fathers, Dearborn, Michigan, July-August, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - LUCHA: Christian Response to Military Repression in Latin America, April 1977, July-August 1977 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - LUX: La Revista de los Trabajadores [broken set], 1979, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Maryknoll, February 1982 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Migration Today, [broken set], 1975, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Migration Today, [broken set], 1977 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Migration Today, [broken set], 1978 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - El Movimiento Sindical Mundial, Mexico, [broken series] February 1973-August 1976 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - NACLA, Report on the Americas, [North American Congress on Latin America], [broken set], 1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - NACLA, Report on the Americas, [North American Congress on Latin America], [broken set], 1978 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - New Generation: Employment of Youth, Education of Migrant Children, National Child Labor Committee, Fall, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - New Perspectives, Journal of the World Peace Council, [broken set], 1976, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - One World, World Council of Churches, September 1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Otro Porque, [broken set], 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - La Raza [broken set, some undated], ca. 1970 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - La Raza [broken set, some undated], ca. 1971 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - La Raza [broken set, some undated], ca. 1971?-1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Revista Politica Semanal, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Rubio's Mexican Financial Journal, [broken set], December 1, 1974- September 15, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - El Salvador Libre, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Servicios de Solidaridad Transfrontera, newsletters, 1979? (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Society, March/April, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Society for Cultural Relations/USA-USSR, bulletin, 1981? (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - The Struggle, October/November 1977, April 1978 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - UPDATE: Latin America, Washington Office on Latin America, August 1979, November/December 1979, July/August 1981, January/February 1981 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - XhismeArte, No.6 [Los Angeles Magazine on politics and art], 1908? (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Labor Issues, 1941-1982, Sub-series 10.F
    - AFL-CIO Los Angeles Counties Organizing Committee, program for meeting Target the Bargaining Table, November 6, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - American Federation of Teachers, article on membership and strike action, September 1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - An Analysis of our AFL-CIO Role in Latin America or Under the Covers with the CIA, by Fred Hirsch, Chairman pro tem, Emergency Committee to Defend Democracy in Chile, (46) pages, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Barnett, Earlie J. v. the International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Southern California Regional Office, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Center Pieces Quarterly Bulletin, Center for Labor Research and Education Institute of Industrial Relations, UCLA, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Chacon, Juan, candidate for President of the United Steelworkers District 38, [covering 14 western states], 1977 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, farmworkers in Florida, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Committee on Political Education (COPE), AFL-CIO Newsletter, April 11, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - La Cooperativa Campesina de California, State of California Migrant Seasonal Farmworkers Council, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Damming [sic] the Migrant Labor Stream, by Joseph Sommers, University of California, San Diego, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Distributive Worker's Union, letter explaining purpose to Department of Consumer Affairs, State of California, June 16, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - La Escuela Laboral del Center for Alternative Education, Inc., course description and posters, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Farm Labor Organizing Committee, news releases, Toledo, Ohio, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Farm Labor Organizing Committee, Conference, Toledo, Ohio, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Farm Labor Organizing Committee, includes (4) 8 × 10 photographs, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Farm Land Workers and Pesticides, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Federación Sindical Mundial, program and reports from the 9th Congress, Prague, Czechoslovakia, [(2) folders], April 16-23, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Federación Sindical Mundial, program and reports from the 9th Congress, Prague, Czechoslovakia, [(2) folders], April 16-23, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Flyers and journal articles on union issues, various unions, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Fyers and Reports, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Immigrant Labor, flyers and information, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Immigration laws, Material for Labor Statement, Congressional Record on Immigration and Nationality Act Amendments of 1973, (25) pages, clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Information on the restrictions on the California fishing industry, reducing the food supply and the job opportunities for minorities, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - International Hod Carriers' and Building Laborers' Union, Local 300 AFL-CIO; Calendar with photographs of construction jobs in California by Carlos Chavez, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - International Ladies Garment Workers Union and undocumented workers, paper, Neutrality, Negligence or Connivance, by Cornelious Wall, Director of Western States Region, I.L.G.W.U., n.d.;clippings, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, 1974, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, biennial conventions, 1975, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union Resolutions on immigration 23rd Biennial Convention, April 23-28, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Testimonial dinner program, June 3, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Junta Laboral, attendance list, July 6, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Kirkland, Lane, Lane's Friends, recent election to the presidency of the AFL-CIO, (2) pages, xeroxed from The Nation, January 19, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Labor Action, flyers, ca. 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Labor and Immigration, flyers and clippings on deportation issues, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Labor Arbitration Services, Workshop Program, September 15-19, November 10-14, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Labor Health and Welfare Information, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Labor newsletters and flyers, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Labor Policy on immigrant workers, flyers and clippings, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Laborers' International Union of North America, Local # 89, San Diego, Resolution, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Leisure World (PCM) labor strike flyer, Local #652, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Lettuce Strike, flyers, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Los Angeles Area Committee for Trade Union Action and Democracy, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Maricopa County Organizing Project (M-Cop), Arizona, clippings on strike, 1977-78 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Mexican-American Classified Employees Association-Los Angeles Unified School District, by-laws, 1976? (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Mexican Workers and Unions in the United States, clippings and flyers, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Mexican Workers and Unions in the United States, clippings and flyers, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Migrant Farmworker: Orientation Material for Community Workers, by the Migrant Legal Action Program, Inc., (3) ring binder, April 1974 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - National Association of Farmworker Organizations, MOVIDAS, [a newsletter], August 22, 1980 and September 26, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - National Council of Distributive Workers, Press release, July 23, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - National Farm Worker Ministry, flyers, 1977, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - National Trade Unionist Committee for Immigrant Workers, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Policy Resolution on illegal immigrants, AFL-CIO, 1971, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Provision House Workers Union, Local 274, AFL-CIO, Los Angeles v. John T. Dunlop, Secretary of Labor, re: election of officers, January 25, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Religion and Labor Conference, Silver Spring, Maryland, October 22, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Santa Ana, California Iron Workers Union, hiring violations, clipping, April 16, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Southwest Labor Studies Association, conference, May 1-3, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Soviet Trade Unions, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Strike in Ventura and Oxnard, California, editorial in Port Hueneme Herald, February 14, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - The Texas Farm Workers Association and the Maricopa County Organizing Project (Arizona) v. The United Farm Workers of America, clipping, February 9, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Texas Farm Workers Union, by Msgr. George G. Higgins, Xerox from The Texas Catholic Herald, August 11, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Torres, Art, United Farm Workers flyer opposing him for Speaker of the Assembly, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Union Committee for All - Labor AIFLD (American Institute for Free Labor Development), 1975 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Union Local 300, Los Angeles, clippings and statements against hiring illegal immigrants, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - United Auto Workers, clippings, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - United Domestic Workers, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - United Farmworkers constitutional convention, Fresno, California, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - United Farmworkers, flyers and newsletters on undocumented workers, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - United Farm Workers, resolutions and clippings, 1976, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - United Professors of California, AFT\AFL-CIO, ballot and literature, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Wage and Salary survey in Los Angeles County and Southern California, March 1, 1975 and March 1, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Warehouse, Processing & Distribution Workers Union (ILWU), contract with American Bravo Co., January 15, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - What's Happening to Labor, by Gil Green, issued by International Publishers, (14) pages, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - World Federation of Trade Unions, 9th Congress, Prague, Czechoslovakia, mailing lists and information, April 16-23, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - World Trade Union Movement: Review of the W.T.U.M., (3) articles: Workers Must Mobilize to Resist Attacks by Big Capital, by John Dyer; A Coalition of Black Trade Unionists is Set Up, no author; The WFTU and Migrant Workers, no author, no. 4, April 1974 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Legal Defense and Lawyers Associations, 1942-1981, Sub-series 10.G
    - Acosta, Carlos, v. John Gaffney, deportation appeal by a U.S. born infant for her alien parents, ca. 1978 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Aliens Have Rights, Too! by Edward Weinstein and Gary Lieberman, Interalia, Journal of the Nevada State Bar, January 1977 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Alondra Park, tenants' rights, Compton, California, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, Civil Liberties and Criminal Code Reform, position paper on the Criminal Code Reform Act of 1980, April 1980 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - American Civil Liberties Union of Southern California, Report on the Committee on Immigration Policy, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - American Civil Liberties Union v. Immigration and Naturalization Service, to stop raids, filed June 22, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Apprehension of undocumented persons, statistics from the Legal Aid Foundation of Los Angeles, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Bail and Deportation hearings, by William B. Taffet, Special Inquiry Officer, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Bill of Rights and the Foreign Born, by Ira Gollobin, February 22, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Blackie's v. Leonel J. Castillo, et al., for illegal search for alien employees, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - California Rural Legal Assistance (CRLA), Conference, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Salvatore B. Castro, et al. v. Superior Court of the State of California for the County of Los Angeles, 2nd Civil no. 34178, S/ct #A-2320-2 filed July 17, 1970. Judicial opinions regarding appeal to dismiss a case against a high school student demonstration ca. 1967[school district?] (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - La Causa Legal Defense Fund and La Causa publications, ca. 1976 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Coalition to Stop Campus Immigration Arrests, (Los Angeles), v. INS & California State University, L.A., 1981 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Deportation material on procedures and defense, ca. 1973 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Immigration laws and practices and the Bill of Rights, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Immigration Newsletter, mimeographed, National Lawyers Guild, National Immigration Project, [broken set], 1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Immigration Symposium, National Lawyers Guild, New York City Chapter, February 22, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Interpreter Panel, Department of Benefit Payments, information for interpreters in legal proceedings, 1975-1977 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Legal Aid Directory, California and Washington, D.C., March 1979 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Legal Aid Foundation of Los Angeles, legal briefs, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Los Angeles Center for Law and Justice, by-laws, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Los Angeles County Bar Immigration Legal Assistance Project, Volunteer Training Seminar Syllabus, Spring, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Madrigal, Dolores et al. v. E. J. Quilligan, sterilization case, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Mental Health Law Project, list of publications, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Mexican-American Bar Association, Los Angeles County, invitation to Town Hall Meeting, June 25, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund (MALDEF), Docket of Litigation, April 1975, October 1976;Invitation, 10th Anniversary Dinner, December 6, 1978, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Muñoz v. Bell case, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - National Clients Council, Inc., Conference announcement, Decades of Struggling--Where Do We Go From Here? (memorial to Fannie Lou Hamer, Mississippi Sharecropper), August 3-6, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - National Coalition on the Hanigan Case, Douglas, Arizona, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - National Lawyers Guild, Immigration-Deportation Clearinghouse, Aliens' Wrongs and Aliens' Rights, reprint from The Conspiracy, The Bay Area National Lawyers Guild Newsletter, April 1973 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - National Lawyers Guild, National Immigration Project, challenging the deportation of parents of U.S. Citizen Children, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - National Legal Aid and Defender Association, re: Title XX of the Social Security Act, August 3, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 17)